<resources>
    <string name="app_name">URSkin</string>

    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="signup">Signup</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    //onboarding
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="welcome1">This application aims to predict 10 skin diseases that are commonly occur in the society with a total accura
    of 81%</string>
    <string name="welcome2">URSkin is one of the applications that are still under development by C241-PS48 team as the final project capstone at Bangkit Academy 2024 Batch 1</string>
    <string name="welcome3">* Please check yourself to nearest clinic if the condition is serious to get more accurate result, by using this app you agree with this statement</string>
    <string name="start">Lets Start</string>

    //login
    <string name="login1">Log into\nyour account</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="google">Log in with Google</string>
    <string name="dont">Dont have an account? Sign up</string>

    //signup
    <string name="create">Create Account</string>
    <string name="name">Full name</string>
    <string name="already">Already have account? Click here</string>

    //predict
    <string name="start_predict">Lets Start Predict</string>
    <string name="gallery_only">You only predict images from the gallery</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="predict">Predict</string>

    //result
    <string name="result">Result Predict</string>
    <string name="description">Desctiption</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="desc">Dermatitis is a general term that refers to inflammation of the skin, characterized by symptoms such as redness, swelling, itching, and the formation of lesions or blisters.
        It can result from various causes including allergic reactions, irritants, genetic factors, or underlying medical conditions.
        There are several types of dermatitis, such as atopic dermatitis (eczema), contact dermatitis, and seborrheic dermatitis, each with distinct triggers and characteristics.
        While dermatitis is not contagious, it can significantly impact an individuals comfort and quality of life. </string>
</resources>